{
  "title": "How to describe people: attitude expressions",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "My wife is always ........ when she gets her period and becomes angry at me for no reason at all. ",
      "answers": ["jealous", "talkative", "content", "bad-tempered"],
      "correct": "bad-tempered"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Students at the school where I teach are so ......... They always hand in their homework on time.",
      "answers": ["patient", "lazy", "reliable", "friendly"],
      "correct": "reliable"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Glenn is so ......... He always helps out the underprivileged people in our community. ",
      "answers": ["creative", "reticent", "sociable", "generous"],
      "correct": "generous"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "My little sister is so ........ at school that she is too afraid to ask to go to the toilet. ",
      "answers": ["timid", "intrepid", "tolerant", "envious"],
      "correct": "timid"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Never ask Phoebe to dance while her husband is looking. He always gets so......... of her. ",
      "answers": ["jealous", "responsive", "mortified", "tolerant"],
      "correct": "jealous"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Our new teacher is so ......... If we don't understand something, she goes over it again and again until we do. ",
      "answers": ["lazy", "shy", "patient", "friendly"],
      "correct": "patient"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "I think Indonesian people are so ......... They'll always come up to you in the street and try to practice their English. ",
      "answers": ["friendly", "reliable", "imaginative", "bad-tempered"],
      "correct": "friendly"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Barry loves to talk a lot, doesn't he? In fact, I don't think I've ever met anyone quite as ........ as him. ",
      "answers": ["reserved", "cantankerous", "chatty", "liberal"],
      "correct": "chatty"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Mary's husband is so ......... He never helps her with any of the chores around the house. ",
      "answers": ["vigorous", "dependable", "lazy", "tolerant"],
      "correct": "lazy"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Our English teacher at school is so ......... He is always coming up with new games that help make learning fun. ",
      "answers": ["bland", "creative", "talkative", "trustworthy"],
      "correct": "creative"
    }
  ]
}
